Hello friends, in the previous video I
told you how you can get your car's third
party insurance done online through Gori General
Insurance. Today I will
give you information on how to get third party insurance for your bike. By
clicking on the link given in the description, you can get
third party insurance for your two wheeler in just 2 to 3 minutes by entering your bike's registration number,
that too for
just Rs. 828. So friends, I am
Uttam Patel and let's start today's
video.
Friends, for getting bike insurance,
I have given you the link of the Digit General Insurance website
in my description below.
On clicking the link, this website of Two Digit General Insurance will open in front of you
where you will get both car and bike options.
I have given information on how to get car insurance in my previous video.
Today let's look at bike insurance,
so I select the bike and click on get, then
here your same yesterday's
registration number is being asked, so you have to
enter your registration number here
and below it is being asked whether your
policy has expired, it is not clear yet, so
if you have your  If the vehicle has a
previous policy and has not been experted, then
you will not expect it, otherwise
you have to select an expert. My policy is about to
expire in three-four days,
so I
click on Camp New Price on Tanot Expert. Now that digit is searching for my information of
yesterday on the basis of my vehicle number.
You
can see that here my vehicle's retail
store has been populated like model and
registration date. Below this, Claim
Last Year is written here. So if you
want to take third party insurance, then you should
ignore it, but if you
want to take a pregnancy policy and your
privacy policy is also comprehensive, then the
details of claim foresight in it are
correct as per the previous policy. If I am
making it from a third party, then it will
not make any difference what I select. Now
you have to go to the Complaint Saver mode given twice below,
Third Party. First, let us see
what is covered in Complaint Secure. So, it includes
accident, fire or natural
disaster due to which the
bike gets damaged.  If this bag gets stolen, then a
comprehensive policy can be useful in such a case.
Apart from this,
in Digit Special Benefits, you are getting more than 1000
costs, carriages, 70% discount on pomegranate
juice for easy claim settlement.
And below here you are
getting another option of third party in which
your third party liability is covered. The
premium for both is also starting here.
Apart from this, you
also have to pay 18 percent GST here. If I want to get
third party insurance for my bike, then
I select third party cover here.
Here in third party, third
party property damage and personal damage damage are
covered. Here below you are
showing the option of personal accident cover.
You get accident insurance of Rs 15 lakh for the owner of the distemper, whose
premium is charged at Rs 338 plus 18 percent.
So if you
want to take it, then click here and
continue. Now there will be more details on this page.
Here you have to write the full name of the owner.
First name auto.  The middle name and sir will appear,
you have to enter the correct pin code,
you have to give the email id and mobile number,
after this on continuing, the
details of your bike will be shown like registration
number, bike variant, chassis number, engine number,
call details, if the auto plate is not shown then
you have to fill it or if there is
any mistake in the bike variant then you have to correct it and continue,
if you have
any loan on your bike then you have to give its details here,
you have to click yes here,
you have to write the name of your bank here,
after this the details of the previous policy will also be
automatically displayed here, you have to
check and click on pay now,
you will get many payment options here
like credit card, debit card, net
banking, wallet option like Mobikwik and Paytm, you will get it
here, you will
get the option of credit card, MIC and many other options like UPA and QR code, you can make payment through any option,
I made the
payment through credit card here, my payment has been
successful and by
taking my policy number here  It has arrived and it is written below
that the soft copy of the policy will be sent to my email ID
soon, so let's
check the email, so here you can see
that the payment receipt mail has arrived and within
1 to 2 minutes I have also received the soft copy of the policy on my email ID, so
friends,
now you can easily make a
third party insurance policy for any bike up to two to three hundred and eighty eight cc from your home or office,
you will have to pay a premium of Rs 1350 for a bike with tubing capacity more than 100 cc,
you
can contact our customer care on WhatsApp,
so friends, that's all for today,
how did you like our video today, do
tell us by commenting, if you liked the video then
like and share it and if you have
not subscribed to our channel yet, then what are you
thinking, subscribe now,
keep watching, 20th is Jai Hind